<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Indraja Nambiar | Personal Website</title>
    <link>http://indrajanambiar.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Indraja Nambiar | Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="http://indrajanambiar.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://indrajanambiar.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 13:49:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://indrajanambiar.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Mail id: hello@indrajanambiar.com Address: Indraprastham(HO), Perambra(Po), Kozhikode, Kerala, 673525</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://indrajanambiar.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 12:49:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://indrajanambiar.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Name: Indraja Nambiar Skills: Python, SQL, R, PowerBI, Tableau, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Weka Expertise: Machine Learning, Data Visualization, Data Modeling, Data Mining Hobbies: Singing, Playing musical instrument(Ukulele), Listening to music
You can download my full resume as a PDF file here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://indrajanambiar.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 12:40:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://indrajanambiar.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>1. Fake News Detection : To develop a model which detect and classifies the fake and real news, which is a classic text classification issue.Machine Learning Models Used are Logistic regression, Decision tree, Random forest and KNN.TF-IDF vectorizer is used for feature extraction and tested the efficiency of the classifier using accuracy. The Accuracy, precision, recall, and f1 score of every model is compared, Logistic regression is selected as the best model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://indrajanambiar.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 12:28:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://indrajanambiar.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Indraja Nambiar , and I am a data analyst with a passion for uncovering insights from complex datasets. As a recent graduate with a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science Specialized in Data Analytics and experience in AI Intern and Data Analyst Intern, I am eager to apply my skills to real-world problems and help businesses make data-driven decisions. My technical skills include proficiency in programming languages such as Python, SQL, and R, as well as experience with data visualization tools such as Tableau and Power BI.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
